通常当我们谈论数据传输效率的时候，我们总是在谈论
Typically when we talk about data transfer efficiency, we're talking
限制数据的传输。它降低了带宽
about limiting the amount of data being transferred. That reduces
还有成本，这很正常的一种思路。
the bandwidth and the cost and is generally a pretty
但是在移动设备上那是一个额外因素。当你看到时，
good idea. But on mobile there's an extra factor. As you
事实证明，移动网络接收模块是
can see, it turns out that the cell radio is
设备中最耗电的硬件之一的。所以
one of the biggest battery drainers on the device. So making
让你的数据传输更高效。到头来解决方案就是提高电池的寿命。
your data transfers more efficient. Will also result in improved
现在，要是程序运行更高效
battery life. Now, the basic level being more efficient means spending
就意味着花更少的时间传输数据，减少你的负载，更少的更新
less time transferring less data, reducing your payloads, and updating
通常可以给你省下一些资源。
less often can take you some of the way there,
但是那又如何？时间上能有什么区别？
but then what? Can timing make a difference? It turns
事实证明可以，这个地方我想把他
out that it can, and it's a situation I like
看做"饼干与安卓"问题。
to think of as the cookie Droid conundrum. Do we
我们是否真的用了更大的有效负载来完成更少的下载？或者我们
perform fewer downloads with larger payloads? Or do we perform
是否在恰当的时机用了大量较小的数据传输操作？
lots of small transfers just in time for when we
一个巨大的饼干还是许多小的饼干？
need them? One big cookie or lots of little cookies?
所以，你是怎样认为的呢？
So, what do you think? Should we have
我们是应该用少量的大饼干表示的庞大下载呢？
a smaller number of large downloads illustrated by
还是用大量的小饼干
this big cookie? Or a large number of
表示的小的下载呢？
small downloads, as illustrated by lots of little cookies.